Visit turkision.com for more!
Osman Bey!
You were talking about a sovereign Beylic.
You said you would walk alone.
This is loneliness.
You cannot even protect Sogut which
was entrusted to you by your father.
-What are you going to do now, Osman Bey?
-Yakup Bey!
We will neither entrust these lands to those
who pretend to be good but draw daggers...
...nor to the oppressor, don't worry.
I am not the one whose homeland
was attacked, Osman Bey.
I am not worried.
That sword is on our neck
because we stood against...
...the cruel, because we ruined their game.
You can bow down as you always do, Yakup Bey.
You might live long then.
Alps! Let's go!
Go, Osman... Go.
You will cause many other
problems with that mindset.
-Kanyumaz!
-My Sultan.
Gather all the traders and shopkeepers.
-I have things to say.
-Yes, my Sultan.
He is always waiting in ambush.
He wants us to lose our balance.
We will not fall, Malhun. No matter
what they do, we will stand against them.
Let's wait for Osman Bey to go to Sogut.
Osman! He took the Princess. He fooled us.
Destroy Sogut!
The people of Yenisehir!
You are all...
...honest traders who are making
great effort to earn halal income.
But... they will even make trades haram for you.
Mongols attacked Sogut.
They can attack Yenisehir anytime.
Osman Bey's moves will put you in trouble.
Listen to me carefully. Your
caravans will be attacked.
Your marketplaces will be raided.
What are you trying to say,
Yakup Bey? Say it directly!
I am trying to say... Traders..
...do not let your Bey use
you for the duality he caused.
Bring your goods to the frontiers marketplace.
Yakup Bey!
While the oppressors are raiding
your brother's homeland, not going...
...to war with them and
trying to gain power here...
...right. It would only suit someone like you.
Those who chose loneliness
while all the people...
...united behind a Sultan pay
the price for their actions alone.
But... there is no need for
our people to pay for this.
I will save them from your hands.
People of Yenisehir! From now on...
...you will not pay a single
tax in the frontiers marketplace.
Thanks to Allah! We will not pay any taxes!
And the safety of your caravans...
...will be provided by Germiyan Alps.
Do not entrust your life and
goods to miserable people...
...who cannot even protect...
..their ancestral homeland.
Yakup Bey is telling the truth!
-Yakup Bey!
Do your best!
Neither we nor our people
will fall for these games!
Come on! You are free to go!
Come on!
They burnt it down, Osman
Bey... They burnt it down.
Indeed, to Allah we belong
and to Allah we shall return/'
You will recover..
We will recover... We will
recover. Don't worry. Alps!
Check the injured ones.
Check everyone! Check the injured ones!
Alps!
What am I going to do? My son..
Don't worry... For sure, we will get
over this. We will treat all our wounds.
What happened here?
Indeed, to Allah we belong
and to Allah we shall return/'
Alps... Alps! My valiants...
My dear... My dear...
My dear...
You killed my innocent
people because you could not...
...take the Princess. You killed my people!
Gorklu Khan! I swear!
I will make you pay for this! Here!
May this baby be my witness!
I will take my revenge from you in
such a way that... In such a way that...
My dear baby... My dear...
Alaeddin.. -My Bey.
-Heal the wounds of all the injured.
-EyvAllah my Bey.
People!
Do not worry!
We will have those dogs..
Pay hundred times more!
-Samil.
-My Bey.
See to everyone needs with the dervish lodge.
As you command, my bey.
My bey. My bey, we couldn't do it.
We couldn't protect our ancestor's lands.
They came so suddenly, my bey.
We tried holding them, however..
People from one side alps from another..
We couldn't my bey, we couldn't.
Osman Bey. Most of my brothers became martyrs.
Gurdogan is no more.
Thank Allah, Talay Alp was here.
He fought like a soldier.
Reduced our losses little bit.
EyvAllah. May you live long, Talay Alp.
It is our duty, my bey. However,
we weren't enough, that is my sorrow.
You got inside the Bannerless. And now..
You will get beside Osman.
We will know his every move, Talay.
Gorklu Khan puts a lot of trust in you.
-I will report everything.
-Come on.
Won't we have them pay for this, my bey?
Of course we will!
When did we not! Do not worry!
We will have them pay for
this a hundred times more!
However first!
First, we will tend to our wounds. After that..
After that, we will be after
that Gorklu Khan always!
-Boran!
-My bey.
Send your most skilled scouts after Gorklu Khan.
-You will find that dog for me.
-As you command, my bey.
My valiants. Valiants.
Alps..
I swear to you. We will have your vengeance.
I will have your vengeance.
Fitnat, let me go. This is Yenisehir, unlike
your frontier marketplace someone can..
Shut it, Ulgen move!
-Fitnat what are you doing? -I said shut it.
Saadet Hatun, what happened?
Who are you? Who are
you to threaten my daughter?
Do you think you are a match
for my daughter just because..
We took you in and fed you?
-Who are you Ulgen?
-I did what I thought was right.
You should ask yourself instead.
What kind of mother would do such..
I would take you
life right here.
I would take your life
however, pray for your child.
You can not understand me.
You need to be as strong as me..
To understand me, Ulgen.
Now, you will say nothing..
To anyone, not a single person. Understood?
I owe a lot to Alaeddin Bey and Kayis.
I won't keep such a thing secret, Saadet Hatun.
Did you hear that, Fitnat?
Ulgen owes a lot to Kayis.
Then, snitch on Cerkutay before Gonca.
-What did Cerkutay do?
-What did he do?
You don't know.
Cerkutay is a spy of Yakup Bey.
He reports everything that Osman Bey does.
No he does not.
My Cerkutay wouldn't do such a thing.
If you do not believe me, ask your husband.
Look, if you tell them a single thing..
I will tell them the real spy is Cerkutay..
And have Osman Bey behead Cerkutay.
Now go, and ask your husband.
Now, we silenced Ulgen.
We gave Alaeddin the response he wanted.
He will know me as the reason
why Gonca stays away from him.
And just like that, our
play will not get exposed.
How will you convince Gonca Hatun?
She nearly told Alaeddin Bey everything.
Fitnat. Every person has weaknesses.
We have a lot to do. Come
on, we will see Bala now.
Konur. Inform the beys of Kayi.
Now, we form the army of Kayi.
I want everyone who can hold a sword!
-As you command, my bey.
-They will be trained..
Until their eyes can not see
and their legs can not hold!
We will form the skilled army of Kayi, my bey.
All of the scouts are after Gorklu Khan, my bey.
As you commanded, they won't leave any
rocks unturned and any tracks unsearched.
Having the princess with
us will damage his reputation.
He'll attempt to attack
us before Ilkhanids hear.
But we will jump on him so we
won't experience this suffering again.
-Horses to go to Yenisehir are ready, my Bey.
-No.
We aren't going to Yenisehir.
He'll attack like a wounded dog.
We won't stop as long as he lives.
We'll build a huge headquarter.
Beys and alps will be with us.
Tell Beys to keep their lands
safe and then come join us.
-Amir Gorklu Khan.
-Yes?
I'll demand horsemen from Konya.
No.
We won't let anyone hear this
issue. We have enough nokers.
Just show me a target, commander.
We've sent nokers all around.
We'll check every place
where the princess may be.
We have a spy beside Osman. We're
waiting for him to send a message.
We won't wait but strike.
Until we find the princess,
we will burn everywhere down.
There will be nowhere still standing!
And then?
They took my wife-to-be, commander.
After I take Maria...
..an army of nokers will come here.
Byzantine army and they will join together.
I will build a tower with..
...the heads of impertinent Turks.
I will sit on it and watch the world!
But the princess first.
Their destination will be the graveyard.
You will have another duty, commander.
Come closer.
We should go to Osman Bey.
Osman's alps are chasing us.
He will come after me.
You will shoot Osman.
I will take the princess.
You won't come to Yenisehir again, Gonca.
-Mother...
-Gonca!
We have much to do in the frontier market.
Alps!
Accompany Gonca Hatun to the frontier market.
Come on.
Saadet Hatun, what do you think you are doing?
You shouldn't provoke people at such times.
Provoking people? Who is doing that?
I'm just telling the truth.
Every move you make is torture to Turks.
Know your place, Saadet.... Hatun.
We torture nobody.
We always work for the welfare of Turks.
Don't confuse us with yourself.
Welfare of Turks, huh? Welfare of Turks?
Didn't you make Mongolians
mess with us for gold?
Didn't the frontier market
get attacked because of you?
Keep yelling! Yell even more. But
you won't be able to reach your purpose.
We will see. Tomorrow.
You'll see when there are
no stalls left in the market.
Nobody trusts you anymore.
Go, Saadet Hatun. Go.
You heard Yakup Bey!
The frontier market will be always open...
...to those who want to
protect their lives and goods.
Oh... Bala.
Tell your son Alaaddin to
stay away from my daughter.
If I see him with her again
I will make him pay for it.
Saadet! You have no power..
...to make my son pay.
If you attempt to touch my
son, I will cut your hand off.
We will see.
Praise be!
There...
This is the spirit to make us a state...
...and make us prevail forever!
-Thank my Creator.
-Thank Allah.
Why did you choose this place as the
headquarter, my Bey? It's away from our borders.
Son, this place...
...is in the right middle of our
tribes around and our other lands.
It's only away from Kestel.
Orhan will protect it, though.
Isn't our priority being close
to Gorklu Khan, my Bey?
No. If he attacks us before we find Gorklu Khan,
...which will never happen,
we will never let that happen.
We need to find him and attack.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
-Any news from the scouts?
-Not yet, my Bey.
My Bey.
This is from Yenisehir, my Bey.
Yakup Bey invites all the merchants...
...to the frontier market.
Because of the attack in Sogut?
Ya Allah... Ya Allah...
My Allah... Now...
If I don't stop now, they'll
call me a brother slayer.
If I stop, my heart won't let me stop.
Yakup Bey...
He's trying to use every
opportunity to attack me. Yakup Bey...
But I won't let him.
-Alaaddin.
-My Bey.
Go to the frontier market.
Keep your eyes on Yakup Bey.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Konur.
Place the watchmen on the hills.
-First, we'll keep the headquarter safe.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Choose the best veterans.
Tell them to train our men.
-As my Bey orders.
My Bey, we've located Gorklu Khan.
Let's go.
You can only know Gorklu Khan if he
wants you to know. Now go towards the trap.
We need to leave before
Orhan comes to take me, Andra.
Come on.
Help me!
What's going on? What is burning?
-What's this smell?
-It's so bad.
This is the door for the secret passage.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER BAZAAR
The cities he ruled are
paying the price for Osman's insolence.
Let those who supported
him see Osman's helplessness.
It seems like Sogut will not
be enough for them, Yakup Bey.
They will...
...keep attacking Osman
until they find the Princess.
If you kidnap Mongols' bride...
-...this is what happens.
-This princess...
What are we going to do,
father? Will we go after her?
-Are we going to wait
and watch both sides?
Since when...
...does a sultan sit and wait?
We will capture the Princess.
I will turn everything upside down.
Then let me get the alps
ready and let's go after them.
No.
You don't need to bother.
We'll cut to the chase.
-May I come in, my Sultan?
-Come in.
You have called me, Sultan Yakup.
I have called you, Cerkutay, I have.
What about you? Have you done
everything I ordered you to do?
-I did my best..
-Shut up!
You can go and track it down if you want.
Or you can find it out from Osman's palace.
Find me the Princess.
Your wish is my command, my Sultan.
-If...
...if you come back empty-handed again, Cerkutay
I'll burn you.
If I burn you, first your loved
ones will be the first to catch fire.
Keep it in mind. Now go away!
Come on!
-My Shahzade!
-I hope nothing is wrong.
-What's going on, Oguz Alp? What happened?
-My Shahzade.
Holofira Hatun tricked the alps and escaped.
What are you saying, Oguz?
How could all those alps not stop
this? Why did I leave you there?
Alps are after her, they
are checking all the places
leading to Atranos. She
left these in her room.
Holofira.
Every flower lives where
it belongs, Orhan. I know
you won't give up, but
don't push it any further.
Don't come after me.
This is better for all of us.
You're right, Holofira. I will not give up.
I'll find you and I'll bring
you back, I'll not give up!
Inform the alps, tell them to set traps
everywhere from Kestel to the valley.
The Frontiers are filled
with enemies, not a single
Crusader will cross to our
homeland from the west.
-Yes, my Shahzade.
-Kara Ali.
-My Shahzade.
-We will find Holofira before dark.
-Come on!
-Yes, my Shahzade.
Come on!
Osman set out to hunt,
soon he will be the prey.
Osman and his followers
will lose their heads!
He will give the princess first,
and then he will give his head.
Commander, Osman is approaching.
Let the wind give wings to his
horse so that he may come quickly.
There are matters to be
settled and blood to be spilled.
avenge my brother!
Nokers, hide.
Come on.
Alps, defend!
Protect the people!
Kill them all.
I'll destroy all the tribes of Osman
...and I'll destroy all of his cities
under the hooves of my horses!
Until we take the Princess...
...peace will be replaced
with blood in these lands.
Attack!
Alps!
Shield formation!
Osman.
Surrender and give us the Princess, so
that your armies and lands can survive.
This land will not be saved by
surrendering but by resisting oppression.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
-Kill the archers.
-Yes, my Bey.
Samil, come, brother.
The Righteous!
These dastards will see the power of Turks.
My glorious armies will conquer your lands.
These lands, conquered after much sufferings,
are the gateway of the Turks to the beyond.
Our adhan will not be silenced
and our banner will not come down.
Father!
Come, girl, let your father go.
-Come here.
-Father! Father!
My brave boys, attack! Kill these murderers!
My power has gone beyond the borders
no one was able to stop,
are you going to stop me?
I'll stop you, and if I can't, those
who come after me will stop you!
I'll rip the courage out of
your heart with my own hands.
You and your father will be destroyed.
Everyone who stands against me will be ruined.
-Where is the princess?
-This fire will burn you too, Mongol.
Osman Bey will...
What is your order, Emir Gorklu Khan?
He is not in Sogut, he is
not in the tribes, from here
to Bursa, burn down all the tribes
all the inns and all the tents!
Sogut incurred the wrath of the Mongols.
Now you too will incur my wrath.
You will kneel before me!
You will pay for what you did to Sogut!
My nokers! Cut their heads off!
Cover!
-You will give me the Princess, Osman.
-The only thing you will take...
...will be the sharp side of my sword!
Your bravery won't save you from death!
You won't die easily... you
shameless Karacelasun!
You did not surrender! Now
you will lose the things you had!
Osman... It is customary to get even.
Now we are stepping back, my
nokers. We will come back stronger.
We will come back with a stronger revenge.
Come! Come here!
You are running again... You are running
again... You shameless Karacelasun...
Alps!
That Karacelasun dog is around. But
Gorklu Khan is no where to be found.
Apparently, he is attacking somewhere.
You will go everywhere! You will
find that dog and bring him to me!
Go now!
And we are going to the
headquarters. No one will sleep tonight.
We have a lot to do. Bring the horses!
Our people are packing the
things on their counters, mother.
Look at what they did... Are they all leaving?
Right... They are all leaving
except for five or six of them, mother.
Then we have no other choice.
Ulgen, Kismet. Send news to Alps.
All doors of Yenisehir will be closed.
Gather all our shopkeepers here.
What are you going to do, mother?
You will see, my daughter.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER BAZAAR
-Stop... Stop.
-Alaeddin...
What were you looking for?
I found what I
was looking for...
Drop that down first. You
were going to slit my throat.
You would have been dead if I hadn't noticed.
-So you would kill me..
-I guess..
You are a merciless Hatun then.
-Alaeddin, what are you doing here?
-I'm on duty.
Are you alright? Your mother
did not do anything to you, right?
-Is it your duty to spy on us?
-Gonca...
Are you not giving me that
answer because of your mother?
Alaeddin... Don't you
see the situation we are in?
I do.
I do, but... It does not seem impossible to me.
What were the answers you couldn't give?
You couldn't speak when your mother came.
Now go. Look, we will be in
trouble if someone sees us. Please.
I will go now. But I am going
because I don't want you to get hurt.
Barbarians! Open the door! Open the door!
Barbarians! You will pay for this!
Princess must get ready
as soon as possible. We
will take her to the place
we prepared in advance.
They found me, right?
No...
It's worse. They attacked.
Barbarians... If you don't let
me go, worse things will happen.
Allah is sufficient for us.
Are we the ones who are barbarians, Princess?
Barbarians are in Byzantium.
Barbarians are Mongols.
Whoever rules with evil is barbarian.
Thanks to us, order has come to these lands.
Islam and justice have come.
And with Allah's consent...
...they will live here forever.
One day you will wake up from
this sleep. You only brought evil.
We are ready to set out, Bayindir Bey.
You cannot abduct me. They
will find me sooner or later.
Princess.
If they plan games, we can plan games.
They won't be able to take you from us and
they won't be able to organize that wedding.
Come on! Get ready! We are leaving!
My Allah... My Allah...
Enemies are always setting traps on our path.
They are always trying to
stop us. But we know that...
You are the Best Planner.
May You grant us with victory, my Allah.
As the branches of the plane tree rise to
the sky, its pain grows, huh, Osman Bey?
Ah, ah Dervish Efendi.
If the plane tree spread all over the world..
...we would not complain about its pain.
-Here, Dervish Efendi. Here. Welcome.
-Thank you.
We wanted to come and see you when we
heard that you were a sovereign Beylic now.
-May it be blessed for all our communiy.
-Thank you, thank you
Enemies are always trying to stop us.
But... there are also people who
get happy about our sovereign Beylic.
Your way is the way of
The Messenger of Allah (PBUH). As you know...
All the wealthy and powerful men of Mecca...
...committed various evil acts to
make the Messenger of Allah give up.
They tried to convince both him
and those who believed in him...
...to leave their path with oppression.
But he did not give up and continued to Tabligh.
(Conveying the message of Islam)
The polytheists of Mecca offered an agreement
to the Prophet (PBUH) as a last resort.
"Let the property be yours
as much as you wish, we will...
...make you the richest and most respected
man in Mecca. Just give up on your path...
...give up on your cause,
do not disturb our order."
The Messenger of Allah said: "My
Allah sent me to you as a Prophet.
He revealed the book to me. If you believe...
...you will be happy both in
this world and in the hereafter.
If you deny it...
...I will wait patiently
until the Judgement Day.
Stop worshiping idols, worship only Allah.
Otherwise, even if you give
me the moon in one hand...
...and the sun in the other hand
I will not give up on my cause.
...and the sun in the other hand,
I will not give up on my cuase."
Now, your path is the path
of the Messenger of Allah.
They will throw thorns at
your feet rather than roses.
But you will walk.
Right. Right.
Our intention is to be
honest and be a good Muslim.
Our cause is the Messenger of Allah's cause.
But... But I know...
...that there were always
people around our the Messenger of Allah
Right... There were Siddiqs who were
ready to sacrifice themselves for him.
O, Dervish Efendi... We have
been talking to you for a long time.
We met through an ant nest and now we are here.
Your words are our light, thank you.
What if... I asked you to tell me your name...
-Would I be going beyond my limit?
-Not at all.
Why would you go beyond the
limit? We are Tapduk's Yunus.
-We are just a poor Dervish.
-Yunus?
Yunus Emre? Are you Yunus Emre?
Oh praise be!
Come, please.
Yunus Emre, huh? Yunus Emre...
Praise be... We have been hearing
your words and poems for a long time!
But you were here! Right next to us...
Oh praise be!
Now you heard our sovereign Beylic, huh?
Then... if you allow me, we
want to see you more often.
As my Allah allows, our roads will unite.
We are always next to people
who are walking on the way of The Righteous
Now allow us please..
Sure, sure.
You can leave. You can leave.
Yunus Emre. Yunus Emre.
They are on foot, must be
close. You will search everywhere.
Everyone will stay on alert! Come on!
-As you command, my shahzade.
You are in this area, daughter of the lord.
You are very close.
Orhan, I know you will be very
angry but this is for your own good.
My lady, we have a long way to Atranos.
I think we have to spend the night
here should we look for places to camp?
We can not stop no matter what
Andra. Orhan must be on our tail by now.
Are you going to strike?
Strike then, daughter of the lord.
-How did you find us?
-I was worried sick Holofira.
What if something happened to you?
When there are nokers and robbers
all around, how can you get away?
You didn't leave me no other choice.
-I didn't leave you any choice?
And this is the solution you came up with?
-Baciyan Holofira.
-You came here for nothing, Orhan.
I won't come back. I am going to Atranos.
My Allah grant me patience.
No. You will come back.
You eyes tell me, you love me.
Now, your home is Kestel.
I won't ever let you go.
Alps! Come on, to Kestel.
As you command, my shahzade.
Orhan, it will be a disaster I tell you.
You refuse to hear me. My aunt will start a war.
Your aunt will start a war?
Alright. Let her start.
One thing I know for sure Holofira..
Is that the winner of that war will be our love.
Come on.
We do not keep anyone by force.
Hear us first. After that doors will be opened.
Anyone can go wherever they want.
Valiant soldiers and brave sisters of Kayi.
Now is the time of unity.
Your life and your goods are
entrusted to us in Yenisehir Marketplace.
Those who attacked Sogut yesterday
won't attack Yenisehir tomorrow?
-Yakup Bey is right, we will leave!
-Yes, we will leave!
Do you really want to leave because
of your life or because of the taxes?
First, ask yourself that!
We will see then. One who rushes
to the gate first is the richest one.
How will you look at your children's
faces after you change your ways for gold?
Salim Aga. Why won't you gather your stall?
Didn't you hear? Yakup Bey is not taxing anyone.
Malhun Hatun.
I owe my life to Osman Bey.
We made a promised on this path.
We won't leave our path, for sure.
EyvAllah Salim Aga. May you live long.
What about you? Those who have sacks of gold?
Don't you owe fidelity to Osman
Bey and to the late Ertugrul Ghazi?
-Why are you leaving up front?
We said what we said.
Our friends stay..
And the door is open for our
enemies. Alps, open the door!
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER BAZAAR
Hatun. Any news from Holofira's aunt?
No. Today Holofira was not
at the marketplace as well.
It needs to be checked and not be left behind.
You're right.
Maiden's house is the house of the coy.
Mehmed. You go and check tomorrow.
Check and hear why Holofira didn't come.
Do not worry, father. I'll check.
After we wed Holofira and Mehmed..
It will be Gonca's turn.
There is still time, mother.
What is it, hatun?
Is there an aspirant for my Gonca?
There is someone who can
not look away from Gonca.
Who is it, mother?
Alaeddin Bey.
Alaeddin Bey the son of Osman?
What are you saying mother?
Gonca, is this true? Answer me!
Brother, calm down.
Do not raise your voice to your sister, Mehmed.
Gonca knows nothing about it.
It seems Alaeddin Bey fell for Gonca.
Soon, they will send a word.
No, mother. I won't let my
sister marry Osman's son.
-Mehmed.
-Father.
Don't you hear my mother? She says Osman.
What? Will you let my sister marry Alaaddin?
I won't answer an unasked question.
Osman will come and ask the question.
And he will get the answer.
Now forget about this.
There will no open stalls in Yenisehir market.
You'll draw all the merchants
to the frontier market.
Don't be worrying, my Bey. We will handle it.
I'm giving this duty to you, Gonca.
You will do it.
As my bey father orders.
-Good.
-Do I have permission, my Sultan?
Come in.
My Sultan, Gorklu Khan is here.
Gorklu Khan?
My Bey, as you ordered, Uraz Bey
and his alps deployed in Taslitepe.
They are waiting on alert in case of an attack.
Salur Bey and his alps
deployed in the woods of Kiragac.
They're waiting for an attack
against Yenisehir and Bilecik.
Either we will stop him or he won't
stop until he takes the princess.
Now send the trained alps
to Inhisar to join Emirhan Bey.
As you order, my Bey.
They attacked Sogut first.
Then they attacked Karakeciler Tribe.
And then, as we heard, they
marched towards the inn of Kirkagac.
It seems..
...they will march to Domanic next.
They'll attack the elder
and the babies in Domanic.
-Say it, Talay Alp.
-50 more alps are ready, my Bey.
-We'll go to Inhisar at dawn. Tell them.
-As you order, my Bey.
My Bey, my alps and I can
leave at night and reach Domanic.
No. We will move at dawn.
I'll tell you when and how to attack.
Okay, my Bey.
Boran, you won't go to fight
with us. You'll take the princess.
For the welfare of our country,
it's important to keep the princess.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Go ahead.
You know the manners, Sultan Yakup.
You didn't welcome me on your throne.
I don't approve your arrival either.
Amir Gorklu Khan.
Where is my princess, Sultan Yakup?
If you thought I have her, you'd have
attacked Kutahya instead of Sogut.
We both know who holds the princess.
Osman is the enemy of both of us.
You are right. But with one difference.
Your enemy, my rival.
Do you want to be crushed
together with him, Yakup?
I neither crush nor get crushed, Amir.
Don't you have enough power to crush Osman?
Yakup, I have a hundred sultans
like you under my command.
They all pay taxes, bow and keep silent.
There is no point in trying
to keep your tail upright.
You know you are much below our power.
If you intend to make me turn against
you, you are walking on the right path.
Those afraid of us cannot be turn against us.
Hear me well now. Bring the princess...
...and I will set you free from Ilkhanids
..taxes and vows.
Think carefully, Sultan.
Mongolian dog!
Come here, fighter. Come.
My Bey, I'm ready. I want
to join the battle, my Bey.
Praise be. Praise be.
Here... Alps!
Look at him. Look at him!
You have this..
...heart of a lion! You all have it!
A heart never trying to get up even if it falls,
...never accepting the defeat...
...and only beating...
...only beating to fight for Islam!
You all have it. All of you.
Here..
This is what makes us different from others.
This is what trust Turkish swords...
..for the freedom of Turks!
Let the others sit comfortably on their chairs!
This is what makes us train in a cold sweat...
...in the middle of night!
A heart beating to fight for Islam!
Tell me.
-What is your heart beating for?
-To fight for Islam, my Bey!
-What is heart beating for?
Praise be! Praise be!
You think we didn't take this into consideration
when we started to establish the state?
We started this journey
at the cost of many fights!
Of course, some bey won't support us.
Of course, some will
attempt to stab us in the back!
Crusaders will attack from all directions.
Mongolians will look for
an opportunity to jump on us!
We know that.
But remember this.
Allah is with us! And
for sure we will be victorious!
Alps, I have the gift of ruling!
-For sure, I will be worthy of the title!
-Yes, my Bey!
But I didn't...
...know only this.
I didn't know Byzantine would
give the princess to Mongolians...
...to defeat us.
Alps! Considering they're
afraid, we are on the right track!
Thank Allah my Bey,
Thank Allah my Bey!
Don't be worrying. For sure
we'll overcome this too.
We will heal our wounds.
We will avenge our martyrs
and our veterans! Don't worry!
Now, tell me. What is your heart beating for?
-For holy war, my Bey!
-What is your heart beating for?
-Praise be!
Praise be.
Alps are ready for the holy war.
Make your final preparations.
-We will hit Gorklu Khan tomorrow.
-Allah is the Greatest!
People will cause bothering,
we need to do something else.
They say it is a matter
of life and death, but
the real issue is taxation,
and this is disloyalty.
Right, first the richest
merchants removed their stalls.
But the stalls of those who are not well remain.
We are getting rid of the rotten
ones, but this will stop our trade.
This will put us in a hard spot, mother.
-No, we will not let that happen.
-Of course we won't.
From now on, we will treat those
who do not listen in a harsh way.
Ulgen.
I said Ulgen.
-Yes?
-What's wrong with you?
You've been very quiet since morning.
No, nothing wrong, I'm all right.
Brother. Did you see Gonca
Hatun after the marketplace?
-I did, she was all right.
-Did you see her?
-Didn't we talk, son?
-I learned the truth, mother.
Mother. Saadet Hatun tried to
slap when she saw Gonca Hatun
-and my brother together.
Look at her, praise be
to my beautiful daughter.
Why haven't you told this until now?
Saadet Hatun forbade Gonca to see me.
What Ulgen Hatun heard was not right.
My Hatun?
Did I do something wrong? Why
are you looking at me like that.
Don't you know what you did, Guice?
Didn't you betray me? Didn't you
rat me out to my mother, Guice?
-Gonca Hatun, I...
-Shush.
I thought you were my friend, Guice.
But you were my mother's friend.
It is over.
I don't want to see you around me again.
Tawba, I will not do it again.
Don't keep me away from you.
No. I don't trust you anymore.
One cannot be a companion with
someone whose back one cannot turn, Guice.
What are you doing here?
I'm getting information from
Guice for my duty, mother.
Today, you disobeyed me again, Gonca.
If I hadn't come, you would
have told Alaeddin everything.
Yes. I was going to, mother. But
you had someone to watch me, right?
Do you know?
When you cannot trust your mother, you
feel like you're all alone in the desert.
You went to that desert
willingly. Do not blame me for it.
You will not disobey me again.
You will not see Alaeddin, Gonca.
I have a duty, if you'll excuse me, mother.
You heard your brother and father.
They know about Alaeddin now.
If he gets close to you, you'll
see what Mehmed will do to him.
Mother, mother, why are you doing this to me?
For you to see. For you to see that
you will not be together with
Alaeddin without my consent.
If you'd listened to me and be reasonable
I was going to convince everyone
and I was going to marry
you off to him on my own.
Don't get excited because your
father didn't say anything at dinner.
She has a suitable groom candidate in his mind.
You wanted this, daughter.
Now you're paying the price of your choices.
My so-called friend turned out
to be my enemy. Alaeddin Bey...
You set eyes on my loved one.
Ah... But
she wouldn't pick him while I'm here.
She would. Shahzade is tall.
And he's strong. And about his intelligence...
...he's one of the most intelligent ones.
He's not ugly, rather, he's pretty handsome.
How am I going to fight with this shahzade?
-Mother?
-What am I going to do?
What am I going to do, what if Saadet is right?
Mother, I'm telling you! I'm losing Gonca Hatun!
-What if Saadet is right?
-Mother?
Osman Bey will not forgive treason.
Cerkutay...
-My Allah, protect us.
-Mother, from what will Allah protect us?
Ulgen Hatun, what are
you doing? You've been
trying to hide every time
you see me since morning.
She's very tense right now, father.
Go. Go to the kitchen and eat halwa, come on.
-Look at me.
-Yes, my Hatun.
Are you spying?
-What are you saying, Ulgen?
-You're spying, that's why you're so afraid.
Cerkutay, what have you done?
How could you do this to Osman Bey?
I didn't do anything. I didn't
say anything to anyone.
-If I did, I tried to gain time...
-You put us in such a hell that...
...there's no way out.
Osman Bey will kill you if he hears about it.
Not only you, he will kill all of us.
-Whoever told this to you...
-I didn't know you at all.
None.
No one knew me.
Who was I?
What was my name?
Cerkutay.
Salah(prayer) is better than sleep
Allah is the Greatest Allah is the Greatest
There is none worthy of worship except Allah,
Allah is the Greatest
May you be safe from evil, and Mercy of Allah be upon you
Tribes and inns are being attacked
but the princess is nowhere to be found.
Our nokers will attack more places.
Where will we march to, Emir Gorklu Khan?
Now, it is time for Domanic.
Tell nokers to prepare.
We won't stop until we have the princess.
Gorklu Khan. Our noker
at Kestel sent his report.
Osman's son Orhan is at Kestel.
-Tell me.
-He is not alone.
Lord's daughter Holofira is with him.
The lone sheep..
Is in danger of who, commander?
The wolf.
Osman. He is playing with my reputation..
By taking the princess.
I will destroy his reputation.
Bring that girl to me.
As you command, Emir Gorklu Khan.
Come on.
Let's see then..
If he will give the princess..
Or not.
My lord, from the spy inside.
Osman.
Knows that we will arrive at Domanic.
Good.
Come on, come on!
Holofira.
I am not hungry.
I am heading out for duty.
Osman Bey is waiting for me.
-However, I wanted to..
-Imprison me.
And you will go now, Orhan?
Mongols. They ambushed Sogut.
-It is bad.
-Jesus Christ protect them.
Holofira look.
Do not try to do what you did yesterday.
Mongols are outside. Do
not make me worry about you.
Mongols you say. If my
aunt comes on top of that..
Look, Orhan. Send me back.
I worry sick that something's
going to happen to you.
Nothing will happen to me Daughter of the Lord.
Now, I want you to promise me.
-To not run.
-No, when I come back..
I will visit the Christian people.
However, if you want to..
Are you trying to soften me up
using the people of my religion now?
You got it quick Holofira Hatun.
Alright. I will help you.
Of course, you can not do without me.
So you will wait for me. You gave me a promise.
From now on, no getting away.
Alright. I will wait, I promise.
However, you will give me a promise as well.
You will come back for sure, alright?
I will.
I will come back..
And look at these eyes again. I promise.
Now I have to go.
However, my heart remains
here, Daughter of the Lord.
You know that.
I know. I know, Orhan.
They're coming.
Let them come. Come on.
So you're the one they call "Gorklu Khan".
And you are the impertinent
Osman, who took my princess.
I know why you are marrying her.
You want to walk over me
by uniting with Byzantine.
You think I would not take the princess..
And let my home get destroyed?
Knowing your place is not bowing to cruelty.
Everyone knows us well. Now you..
Will meet the executioner
of the cruels that is my sword.
And I will have you and those behind you..
Meet my wrath. Nokers!
We do not get scared because you're few..
Or because you're many.
Then I will teach you fear.
It is above you, Osman.
Maybe you will learn it the hard way..
However, if those behind you manage to survive..
They will remember
today in fear for all eternity.
The sheep that knows its death..
Licks the butcher's knife.
You are facing the wrong man, Osman.
We will see. Sheep or wolf.
Now you are in my hunting field.
-Archers!
-Ya Hakk!
Now, the field is ours! Alps, attack!
Come on brothers!
My Bey!
Gorklu!
If there will be no sleep to us,
there will be none to you as well!
Alps! Fall back!
Will we strike Domanic my Emir?
-No.
Let the commander not arrive empty handed.
Osman will bow to me..
With his own hands.
-Come on.
-Nokers.
My lady. Will we wait like this?
We will, Andra. What about your aunt?
-Are you not afraid of her anymore? -I am.
I am very afraid of her.
However, I gave a promise to Orhan. I will wait.
Come on, quickly!
Andra, something bad is happening.
Holofira Hatun, Mongols are attacking.
How did they enter the castle?
Does Orhan knows of this?
They must've bought a guy from
inside. Doors are open, they are inside.
-We will hide you.
-Come on.
-Where is princess's room?
-Ahead.
This is her room.
Come on.
-Where is the rest of the
gold? I brought you here.
Your gold will come.
Commander, princess is missing.
This is her room. How could this
be? She was supposed to be inside.
They will take her from the
passage. We must have her, quickly.
The secret passage is
behind this door. Let us move!
-Where are you going?
-What do you want from me?
Don't be scared. For Princess Maria.
They will give her, and they will take you.
Of course, if they want you.
Now drop your sword.
I will never
surrender to a Mongol!
Look... I do not hurt women.
But her survival is in your hands.
Come on.
Nokers. Take these women.
You will pay for this! You
will not get away with this!
Bahadir Alp is coming, my Shahzade.
My Shahzade! -Bahadir!
Why aren't you in Kestel, huh?
-My Shahzade, Mongols...
What happened to Mongols,
Bahadir? Cut it short, speak!
They sneaked in Kestel.
-Holofira...
Is Holofira safe?
They abducted
Princess Holofira.
Why did I place you there,
huh? What were you doing?
Where did they go? Speak!
We went after them until Cinarbasi, but...
.then we lost them. I gave you horses!
I gave you swords! But you let me down!
I entrusted our lands and people to you!
But you could not protect them! Get lost!
Alps! We are going to
Cinarbasi! No matter what...
...we will save Holofira!
-Yes, my Shahzade.
The injured people are alright,
my Bey. They will recover.
But I didn't understand how we fell for
an ambush while going for an ambush.
We stopped the Domanic raid...
It's about that. But the actual issue is...
...getting raid while going for a raid.
It means there is a spy among us.
But we know who it is.
Talay dog.
First, he took advantage of
the injured people in Sogut.
Thanks to Allah, Talay Alp
was here. He fought like a man.
He made up a story to show himself as a hero.
It was our duty, my Bey. But I feel
sorry because we were not enough.
He approached us to hear
the details about Domanic raid.
And the ambush... He did his
best to avoid killing Mongols.
It was that dog who made
our move unsuccessful...
...it was him, but... We will
plan the actual game over him.
Ours is the dream of a
glorious state ruling the world.
We will not let the cruel and the traitors win.
Whoever comes, for sure we will crush them.
Sure my Bey. How
will we plan our game then?
They want the Princess.
I will give them the Princess.
Won't you talk to me, Gonca Hatun?
I had to.
Saadet Hatun gave me the duty. What could I do?
She doesn't even pity you.
What would she do to me if I didn't tell her?
If you had told me, I'd have found a solution
But you acted behind my back, Gulce.
Saadet Hatun sent news to The Sisters
to marry you.
-What?
-I heard them talking.
She'll do what she has said.
She'll make me marry someone.
Don't let her find out I told you.
I won't do anything without informin you again.
Gonca Hatun. The caravans are approaching.
Good. Let's welcome them.
Come on! Come on!
Mother... What will happen if the goods do not arrive?
Then we will find another solution, my daughter.
Welcome... Welcome Malhun Hatun.
Kayi's loyal, foul-weather friends...
...brothers, sisters...
You never hesitated to stand behind us.
You never stepped back. Thank you all!
Thank you, Malhun Hatun. May Allah bless you.
Ulgen... Tell the clerk to write down the names of our traders.
From now on, all the needs in the Bey Palace will be
purchased from these counters.
None of their goods will be wasted.
May Allah bless you!
May Allah bless you..
Haven't you heard from your brother yet, my daughter?
I am sorry, my brother... I could only last this long.
What happened?
Mother... I can't
stand it anymore.
My brother.. -What?
..abducted Holofira.
What are you saying, Fatma?
Why haven't you told me?
Don't be angry with me, it's not my fault, mother.
Oh, Orhan.
Malhun Hatun.
Malhun Hatun, Karacelasun attacked Kestel.
He kidnapped Holofira Hatun.
My Allah, protect us.
-Konur, tell me. How's it going?
-As you ordered, my Bey.
Some of the alps are in Domanic.
Domanic
is not the target anymore.
The news is about to reach Tabriz.
Gorklu Khan will attack even harder.
As long as he cannot find the Princess, he will try all the lands.
What is your order, my Bey?
We'll go all the way. We will not stop.
If we are going to be destroyed
we will take him with us.
Inform Boran, tell him to
take the Princess to Taskesen.
It is the safest place for now.
Yes, my Bey.
-Make preparations.
-Yes, my Bey.
Come on alps.
Stop!
What are you doing, Bala Hatun? Shahzade Alaeddin?
Those who do not stand by their friends in bad times
should not stand by them in good times.
Turn the cars around, the goods will go to Yenisehir.
We said what we had to say, we will trade
in the frontier marketplace from now on.
You've heard my Valide.
Do not make her repeat, turn the cars around!
I know how fond you are of money. Don't worry.
You'll get plenty of money back.
We don't violate anyone's right.
Kismet, give them their money.
Hasan. Memorize all the merchants here one by one.
From now on, they will not be able to trade in Kayi lands.
-Let everyone know.
-Yes, my Shahzade.
My Shahzade, what are we going to do?
Who are we going to trade with?
What's going on here?
Bala Hatun? Alaeddin Bey?
We've taken what is ours, we're leaving, Gonca Hatun.
Come on, let's take the cars.
You intimidate traders who voluntarily come to the
frontier marketplace and threaten them into turning back.
I won't let you do that. Sisters!
We're not threatening anyone.
We've given their money and we've taken the goods.
We said that we will cut the trade if they go to frontier marketplace.
-Here's the path, they can go if they want.
-No.
This is not right, Bala Hatun.
Trickster Hatun. Go back to your marketplace.
It is my duty to protect these merchants, Alaeddin Bey, do not stop me.
Your father deceived our merchants.
I told you not to talk badly about my father.
Do not force me to do things I do not want to do.
Enough!
Tell me now, do you still want to go to the frontier marketplace?
Whoever is going to take goods to the frontier marketplace
should take his bed and go. -Let them come!
They are more than welcome.
Yakup Bey's marketplace and lands are open to anyone, thanks to Allah.
We do not need people who sell their homeland for money, the choice is yours.
We are going back to Yenisehir, then.
And we will go to the frontier marketplace.
Very well the, come on. Let everyone go their own way.
Come on sisters, we're leaving.
Come on.
What are you looking at?
What will you ask for? Tell me.
Make way.
The end of your barbarism will be disastrous for you.
I swear by Jesus Christ.
They will kill you all when they find me.
I will watch it with pleasure.
No one can find you as long as we do not want it.
Forget about it, do not get excited for it, Princess.
I can see the fear in your eyes, Turk.
I'm sure that Gorklu Khan is close, otherwise
why would we switch places so often?
It's refreshing to change places, why else would we do it?
We've been on the road for so long, you must be hungry, here.
I don't want it.
I will not eat your food. Insolent Turks.
If you wait for them to find you, you'll starve to death.
-Just saying.
-I'd rather die honorably
-than eat your food.
-EyvAllah.
We have news from Osman Bey.
Come on, Princess.
We're leaving.
Near Osman Bey's Headquarters
You'll die when Gorklu Khan finds out about Princess, Osman.
Osman Bey!
Osman Bey, right.
Look at me. Look at me.
You inform Gorklu Khan about every move I make, is that so?
You ambushed me when I went to lay an ambush, is that so?
Osman... So you opened your eyes.
But it is too late now.
Gorklu Khan knows about Princess.
But you will die now!
Look at me. Look at me!
I knew about you before.
But you are the one...
...to take me to Gorklu Khan.
Princess... A trap, huh?
Yes. He will go to the death while going to the princess.
Get him up.
I will walk on the path...
..of being a state with solid steps.
But you the cruel... You the treacherous...
..will be crushed under my feet...
...on my path.
I won't forgive anyone against me for this cause.
I will crush everyone.
What is next, my Bey?
Prepare this dog for Gorklu Khan.
Okay, my Bey.
Come on, alps.
Come on!
I will move with the ones here.
I will shut their mouths.
Let's go.
You're putting me in a hard situation.
Anyone can hear or see!
Only you concern me now
Oh really? What happened?
You weren't saying so before.
Before, we both were doing our duties.
But when it comes to duty, you get angry.
Scholar.
My mother told my brother and father about you.
-Did they say anything to you?
-No.
-She didn't tell them she saw us together.
-Fine. No problem then.
Is this fearlessness too much?
I'm afraid of only one thing.
Words to come out of this beauty's mouth.
Come on. Give me your answer.
This is too hard, Scholar. My brother got mad
when he even heard your name.
Sorry but Mehmed Bey is always mad.
Tell me now. Is your heart beating together with mine?
They always called me Gonca the Fearless, you know.
Until you came into my life.
I have fears.
My heart and mind are always on alert.
They always miss you and and want to know about you.
You aren't going to kill me with your sword, but your words.
Since the day I first saw you
...my heart has been beating together with yours, Alaaddin Ali.
Allah! Allah Allah! Allah!
Thank you, my Allah
-Allah!
-Stop!
-Stop, you crazy.
-No! We won't wait anymore.
I will talk to my father. We'll go talk to your father.
Trails stop here.
-Karaali.
-My Shahzade.
You got that way. Oguz Alp, you go that way.
Don't come back without trails!
Where are you, Holofira?
-Where are you?
-My Shahzade.
I found this a little ahead, up there.
Holofira's dagger. You found it there?
-That way.
-Alps, let's go!
-Holofira!
-Orhan! Don't come! Trap!
Osman's baby! I knew you'd come after me.
Surrender so both you...
..and your woman will live.
I'd rather die than surrender to a dog like you!
Nokers, I want Orhan alive. Attack!
Orhan... You will never give up, will you?
-Orhan!
-Holofira!
You dog, I will come after you.
I will take first the hatun and then your head!
Yes, yes... A dog can only be tested with a dog.
You aren't even equal to my dog.
Nokers, tie her up.
Holofira.
Princess.
-Amir Gorklu Khan.
-Maria.
Osman! Osman!
Osman!
Gorklu Khan!
Osman.
I told you! There are the predator and the prey!
-You are in my hunting territory.
-Osman.
Your impertinence is limitless.
Your everything belong to Ilkhanids. You will learn that.
Preys are mine!
Everything is mine!
I have...
...both your son and his wife Holofira.
What?
Now I will walk freely out of here.
And you will bring my princess to me.
Look at me. Look at me!
If they are hurt even slightly.
you can find no place in these lands to hide in!
You should know that!
Visit turkision.com for more!